const e={sections:[{header:{text:"Choose the correct option"},exercises:[{type:"test",question:"Dinara said that she ____ keen on Math.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"was",2:"is",3:"has been",4:"were"}},{type:"test",question:"I told her that I ____ time to do my home task that time.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"did not have",2:"have no",3:"did not have",4:"had not have"}},{type:"test",question:"Vanya answered that he ____ very early, so he ____ the phone call.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"went to bed, hadn't heard",2:"had gone to bed, hadn't heard",3:"has gone to bed, hasn't heard",4:"had gone to bed, didn't hear"}},{type:"test",question:"Cristina told me that she ____ to leave for Almaty the next week.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"was going",2:"is going",3:"were going",4:"has gone"}},{type:"test",question:"I replied that I ____ her when I ____ back.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"would phone, got",2:"will phone, got",3:"will have phoned, will have come",4:"is to phone, get"}},{type:"test",question:"Vanya says that Almaty ____ beautiful in spring.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"is",2:"was",3:"has been",4:"were"}},{type:"test",question:"Mother said that Katya ____ worry about her health.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"was",2:"were",3:"are",4:"is"}},{type:"test",question:"I said that I ____ if I ____ time.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"would go, had",2:"will go, have",3:"would go, have had",4:"will go, had"}},{type:"test",question:"Dinara answered that she ____wake up early in the morning when she was young.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"used to",2:"did get used to",3:"gets used to",4:"is getting used to"}},{type:"test",question:"I am surprised to see you. Your mother said you ____ ill.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"were",2:"has been",3:"are",4:"had been"}},{type:"test",question:"She said that Marat ____ into his flat because he ____ her key.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"couldn't get, had lost",2:"cannot get, lost",3:"couldn't get, has lost",4:"can't get, was losing"}},{type:"test",question:"Jane told everybody that she ____ a meeting____ .",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"would having, the next day",2:"had, tomorrow",3:"was having, tomorrow",4:"will have, the next day"}},{type:"test",question:"Mary tells me that passing an exam ____ her nervous.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"makes",2:"was making",3:"will make",4:"made"}},{type:"test",question:"Vasilisa said that she ____ in Kokshetau for one year.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"had been living",2:"lived",3:"had lived",4:"lives"}},{type:"test",question:"They said that we ____ when Aruzhan ____ .",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"would leave, came",2:"will leave, came",3:"would leave, comes",4:"would leave, had come"}}]}]};export{e as default};
